var wordsData = [
    // "一"
    {answer: "いちばん", question: "一番", hint: "number one", sound: "いち", kanji:"一"},
    {answer: "いっしょ", question: "一緒", hint: "together", sound: "いっ", kanji:"一"},
    {answer: "ひとり", question: "一人", hint: "one person", sound: "ひと", kanji:"一"},
    {answer: "ゆいいつ", question: "唯一", hint: "only one", sound: "いつ", kanji:"一"},
    // "七"
    {answer: "なな", question: "七", hint: "seven", sound: "なな", kanji:"七"},
    {answer: "しちめんどう", question: "七面倒", hint: "very troublesome", sound: "しち", kanji:"七"},
    {answer: "なのか", question: "七日", hint: "seventh day", sound: "なの", kanji:"七"},
    // "万"
    {answer: "ばんぜん", question: "万全", hint: "perfection", sound: "ばん", kanji:"万"},
    {answer: "まんがいち", question: "万が一", hint: "once in a million", sound: "まん", kanji:"万"},
    {answer: "やおよろずのかみ", question: "八百万の神", hint: "all the gods and goddessses", sound: "よろず", kanji:"万"},
    // "三"
    {answer: "さんかく", question: "三角", hint: "triangle", sound: "さん", kanji:"三"},
    {answer: "みつどもえ", question: "三つ巴", hint: "triplet", sound: "み", kanji:"三"},
    {answer: "みつびし", question: "三菱", hint: "mitsubishi", sound: "みっ", kanji:"三"},
    // "上"
    {answer: "いじょう", question: "以上", hint: "more than", sound: "じょう", kanji:"上"},
    {answer: "まうえ", question: "真上", hint: "right above", sound: "うえ", kanji:"上"},
    {answer: "あがる", question: "上がる", hint: "raise", sound: "あ", kanji:"上"},
    {answer: "うわまわる", question: "上回る", hint: "to exceed", sound: "うわ", kanji:"上"},
    {answer: "のぼる", question: "上る", hint: "climb", sound: "のぼ", kanji:"上"},
    {answer: "おかみ", question: "御上", hint: "empress", sound: "かみ", kanji:"上"},
    {answer: "うりあげ", question: "売上", hint: "sale(improved)", sound: "あげ", kanji:"上"},
    // "下"
    {answer: "いか", question: "以下", hint: "less than", sound: "か", kanji:"下"},
    {answer: "したぎ", question: "下着", hint: "underwear", sound: "した", kanji:"下"},
    {answer: "みくだす", question: "見下す", hint: "look down", sound: "くだ", kanji:"下"},
    {answer: "さがる", question: "下がる", hint: "decrease", sound: "さ", kanji:"下"},
    {answer: "しもねた", question: "下ネタ", hint: "dirty joke", sound: "しも", kanji:"下"},
    {answer: "とびおろす", question: "飛び下す", hint: "jump down", sound: "お", kanji:"下"},
    {answer: "げひん", question: "下品", hint: "vulgar", sound: "げ", kanji:"下"},
    {answer: "しどうのもとに", question: "指導の下に", hint: "under the guidance", sound: "もと", kanji:"下"},
    // "中"
    {answer: "なかみ", question: "中身", hint: "inside", sound: "なか", kanji:"中"},
    {answer: "とちゅう", question: "途中", hint: "on the way", sound: "ちゅう", kanji:"中"},
    {answer: "みないうち", question: "見ない中", hint: "while", sound: "うち", kanji:"中"},
    // "九"
    {answer: "きゅうび", question: "九尾", hint: "nine tail", sound: "きゅう", kanji:"九"},
    {answer: "だいく", question: "第九", hint: "ninth", sound: "く", kanji:"九"},
    {answer: "ここのか", question: "9日", hint: "ninth day", sound: "ここの", kanji:"九"},
    // "二"
    {answer: "にどと", question: "二度と", hint: "never twice again", sound: "に", kanji:"二"},
    {answer: "ふたり", question: "二人", hint: "two person", sound: "ふた", kanji:"二"},
    {answer: "しんどふじ", question: "身土不二", hint: "you are what you eat", sound: "じ", kanji:"二"},
    // "五"
    {answer: "ごかん", question: "五", hint: "five", sound: "ご", kanji:"五"},
    {answer: "いそじ", question: "五十路", hint: "age fifty", sound: "い", kanji:"五"},
    {answer: "いつか", question: "五日", hint: "fifth day", sound: "いつ", kanji:"五"},
    {answer: "さつき", question: "五月", hint: "fifth month", sound: "い", kanji:"五"},
    // "人"
    {answer: "こいびと", question: "恋人", hint: "lover", sound: "ひと", kanji:"人"},
    {answer: "にんげん", question: "人間", hint: "human", sound: "にん", kanji:"人"},
    {answer: "じんせい", question: "人生", hint: "life", sound: "じん", kanji:"人"},
    {answer: "ひとり", question: "一人", hint: "alone", sound: "り", kanji:"人"},
    {answer: "すけっと", question: "助っ人", hint: "helper", sound: "と", kanji:"人"},
    // "今"
    {answer: "いまさら", question: "今更", hint: "too late now", sound: "いま", kanji:"今"},
    {answer: "こんど", question: "今度", hint: "this time", sound: "こん", kanji:"今"},
    // "休"
    {answer: "ひるやすみ", question: "昼休み", hint: "lunch break", sound: "やす", kanji:"休"},
    {answer: "きゅうけい", question: "休憩", hint: "break", sound: "きゅう", kanji:"休"},
    // "会"
    {answer: "かいしゃ", question: "会社", hint: "company", sound: "かい", kanji:"会"},
    {answer: "であい", question: "出会い", hint: "meeting", sound: "あ", kanji:"会"},
    {answer: "いちごいちえ", question: "一期一会", hint: "once in a lifetime", sound: "え", kanji:"会"},
    // "何"
    {answer: "なにげなく", question: "何気なく", hint: "casually", sound: "なに", kanji:"何"},
    {answer: "なんばいも", question: "何倍も", hint: "manyfold", sound: "なん", kanji:"何"},
    {answer: "きかがく", question: "幾何学", hint: "geometry", sound: "か", kanji:"何"},
    // "先"
    {answer: "せんぱい", question: "先輩", hint: "senior", sound: "せん", kanji:"先"},
    {answer: "ゆびさき", question: "指先", hint: "fingertip", sound: "さき", kanji:"先"},
    {answer: "まず", question: "先ず", hint: "first", sound: "ま", kanji:"先"},
    // "入"
    {answer: "おそれいる", question: "恐れ入る", hint: "sorry", sound: "い", kanji:"入"},
    {answer: "はいりこむ", question: "入り込む", hint: "go into", sound: "はい", kanji:"入"},
    {answer: "しんにゅうしゃいん", question: "新入社員", hint: "new employee", sound: "にゅう", kanji:"入"},
    {answer: "たちいりきんし", question: "立入禁止", hint: "prohibited area", sound: "いり", kanji:"入"},
    // "八"
    {answer: "しゃくはち", question: "尺八", hint: "blowjob", sound: "はち", kanji:"八"},
    {answer: "やおや", question: "八百屋", hint: "green grocer", sound: "や", kanji:"八"},
    {answer: "しほうはっぽう", question: "四方八方", hint: "all direction", sound: "はっ", kanji:"八"},
    // "六"
    {answer: "ろく", question: "六", hint: "six", sound: "ろく", kanji:"六"},
    {answer: "ろっかん", question: "六感", hint: "six sense", sound: "ろっ", kanji:"六"},
    {answer: "むっつ", question: "六つ", hint: "six things", sound: "むっ", kanji:"六"},
    // "円"
    {answer: "えんしゅうりつ", question: "円周率", hint: "PI", sound: "えん", kanji:"六"},
    // "出"
    {answer: "おもいで", question: "思い出", hint: "memories", sound: "で", kanji:"出"},
    {answer: "おもいだす", question: "思い出す", hint: "realized", sound: "だ", kanji:"出"},
    {answer: "しゅっぱつ", question: "出発", hint: "departure", sound: "しゅっ", kanji:"出"},
    // "分"
    {answer: "ぶんせき", question: "分析", hint: "analysis", sound: "ぶん", kanji:"分"},
    {answer: "やまわけ", question: "山分け", hint: "equal division", sound: "わ", kanji:"分"},
    // "前"
    {answer: "うでまえ", question: "腕前", hint: "ability", sound: "まえ", kanji:"前"},
    {answer: "ちょくぜん", question: "直前", hint: "immediately", sound: "ぜん", kanji:"前"},
    // "北"
    {answer: "ほくとう", question: "北東", hint: "northeast", sound: "ほく", kanji:"北"},
    {answer: "ほくせい", question: "北西", hint: "northwest", sound: "ほく", kanji:"北"},
    {answer: "きたかぜ", question: "北風", hint: "north wind", sound: "きた", kanji:"北"},
    {answer: "ほっかいどう", question: "北海道", hint: "city", sound: "ほっ", kanji:"北"},
    // "十"
    {answer: "じゅうぶｎ", question: "十分", hint: "enough", sound: "じゅう", kanji:"十"},
    {answer: "じゅっかい", question: "十回", hint: "ten times", sound: "じゅっ", kanji:"十"},
    {answer: "とおか", question: "十日", hint: "tenth day", sound: "とお", kanji:"十"},
    {answer: "みそじ", question: "三十路", hint: "age thirty", sound: "そ", kanji:"十"},
    // "千"
    {answer: "せん", question: "千", hint: "thousand", sound: "せん", kanji:"千"},
    {answer: "ちばけん", question: "千葉県", hint: "city", sound: "ち", kanji:"千"},
    // "午"
    {answer: "ごはん", question: "午飯", hint: "lunch", sound: "ご", kanji:"午"},
    {answer: "ひのえうま", question: "丙午", hint: "fire horse", sound: "うま", kanji:"午"},
    // "半"
    {answer: "かはんしん", question: "下半身", hint: "lower body", sound: "はん", kanji:"半"},
    {answer: "なかば", question: "半ば", hint: "half", sound: "なか", kanji:"半"},
    // "南"
    {answer: "なんとう", question: "南東", hint: "southeast", sound: "なん", kanji:"南"},
    {answer: "なんせい", question: "南西", hint: "southwest", sound: "なん", kanji:"南"},
    {answer: "みなみはんきゅう", question: "南半球", hint: "southern hemisphere", sound: "みなみ", kanji:"南"},
    {answer: "なむあみだぶつ", question: "南無阿弥陀仏", hint: "god bless", sound: "な", kanji:"南"},
    // "友"
    {answer: "ともだち", question: "友達", hint: "friend", sound: "とも", kanji:"友"},
    {answer: "ゆうじん", question: "友人", hint: "best friend", sound: "ゆう", kanji:"友"},
    // "口"
    {answer: "くちぶえ", question: "口笛", hint: "whistle", sound: "くち", kanji:"口"},
    {answer: "こうざ", question: "口座", hint: "bank account", sound: "こう", kanji:"口"},
    {answer: "くどく", question: "口説く", hint: "persuade", sound: "く", kanji:"口"},
    // "古"
    {answer: "こだい", question: "古代", hint: "ancient time", sound: "こ", kanji:"古"},
    {answer: "ふるぎ", question: "古着", hint: "old clothes", sound: "ふる", kanji:"古"},
    // "右"
    {answer: "みぎきき", question: "右利き", hint: "right handed", sound: "みぎ", kanji:"右"},
    {answer: "うよく", question: "右翼", hint: "right dominant", sound: "う", kanji:"右"},
    {answer: "じょうげさゆう", question: "上下左右", hint: "up down left right", sound: "ゆう", kanji:"右"},
    // "名"
    {answer: "なごや", question: "名古屋", hint: "city", sound: "な", kanji:"名"},
    {answer: "ゆうめい", question: "有名", hint: "famous", sound: "めい", kanji:"名"},
    {answer: "ほんみょう", question: "本名", hint: "real name", sound: "みょう", kanji:"名"},
    // "四"
    {answer: "よん", question: "四", hint: "four", sound: "よん", kanji:"四"},
    {answer: "しき", question: "四季", hint: "four season", sound: "し", kanji:"四"},
    {answer: "よにん", question: "四人", hint: "four peoples", sound: "よ", kanji:"四"},
    {answer: "しゅうよっか", question: "週四日", hint: "four days a week", sound: " よっ", kanji:"四"},
    // "国"
    {answer: "ていこく", question: "帝国", hint: "empire", sound: "こく", kanji:"国"},
    {answer: "くに", question: "国", hint: "country", sound: "くに", kanji:"国"},
    // "士"
    {answer: "しんし", question: "紳士", hint: "gentleman", sound: "し", kanji:"士"},
    {answer: "しかん", question: "士官", hint: "officer", sound: "し", kanji:"士"},
    // "外"
    {answer: "いがい", question: "意外", hint: "unexpected", sound: "がい", kanji:"外"},
    {answer: "そとまわり", question: "外回り", hint: "work outside", sound: "そと", kanji:"外"},
    {answer: "はずれ", question: "外れ", hint: "miss", sound: "はず", kanji:"外"},
    {answer: "げか", question: "外科", hint: "surgery", sound: "げ", kanji:"外"},
    // "多"
    {answer: "おおい", question: "多い", hint: "a lot", sound: "おお", kanji:"多"},
    {answer: "たぶん", question: "多分", hint: "maybe", sound: "た", kanji:"多"},
    // "大"
    {answer: "たいかい", question: "大会", hint: "tournament", sound: "たい", kanji:"大"},
    {answer: "おおさか", question: "大阪", hint: "city", sound: "おお", kanji:"大"},
    {answer: "おとな", question: "大人", hint: "adult", sound: "お", kanji:"大"},
    // "天"
    {answer: "てんさい", question: "天才", hint: "", sound: "てん", kanji:"天"},
    {answer: "あまのがわ", question: "天の川", hint: "", sound: "あま", kanji:"天"},
    // "女"
    {answer: "かのじょ", question: "彼女", hint: "girlfriend", sound: "じょ", kanji:"女"},
    {answer: "おんな", question: "女", hint: "woman", sound: "おんな", kanji:"女"},
    {answer: "おとめ", question: "乙女", hint: "maiden", sound: "め", kanji:"女"},
    {answer: "にょごのしま", question: "女護の島", hint: "virgin island", sound: "にょ", kanji:"女"},
    // "子"
    {answer: "こども", question: "子供", hint: "child", sound: "こ", kanji:"子"},
    {answer: "でんしおん", question: "電子音", hint: "electronic sound", sound: "し", kanji:"子"},
    {answer: "ようすみ", question: "様子見", hint: "wait and see", sound: "す", kanji:"子"},
    // "学"
    {answer: "かがく", question: "科学", hint: "science", sound: "がく", kanji:"学"},
    {answer: "まなび", question: "学び", hint: "learning", sound: "まな", kanji:"学"},
    // "安"
    {answer: "あんしん", question: "安心", hint: "safe", sound: "あん", kanji:"安"},
    {answer: "やすうり", question: "安売り", hint: "bergain sale", sound: "やす", kanji:"安"},
    // "小"
    {answer: "しょうがく", question: "小学", hint: "elementary class", sound: "しょう", kanji:"小"},
    {answer: "こゆび", question: "小指", hint: "pinky", sound: "こ", kanji:"小"},
    {answer: "ちいさい", question: "小さい", hint: "small", sound: "ちい", kanji:"小"},
    {answer: "おがわまち", question: "小川町", hint: "-town name-", sound: "お", kanji:"小"},
    // "少"
    {answer: "すこし", question: "少し", hint: "few", sound: "すこ", kanji:"少"},
    {answer: "たしょう", question: "多少", hint: "little", sound: "しょう", kanji:"少"},
    {answer: "すくない", question: "少ない", hint: "not enough", sound: "すく", kanji:"少"},
    // "山"
    {answer: "やまおく", question: "山奥", hint: "deep in the mountains", sound: "やま", kanji:"山"},
    {answer: "かざん", question: "火山", hint: "vocalno", sound: "さん", kanji:"山"},
    // "川"
    {answer: "かわ", question: "川", hint: "river", sound: "かわ", kanji:"川"},
    {answer: "かせん", question: "河川", hint: "rivers", sound: "せん", kanji:"川"},
    // "左"
    {answer: "ひだりきき", question: "左利き", hint: "left-handed", sound: "ひだり", kanji:"左"},
    {answer: "さほう", question: "左方", hint: "left side", sound: "さ", kanji:"左"},
    // "年"
    {answer: "としごろ", question: "年頃", hint: "appropriate age", sound: "とし", kanji:"年"},
    {answer: "ねんれい", question: "年齢", hint: "age", sound: "ねん", kanji:"年"},
    // "店"
    {answer: "ひゃっかてん", question: "百貨店", hint: "department store", sound: "てん", kanji:"店"},
    {answer: "みせばん", question: "店番", hint: "salesperson", sound: "みせ", kanji:"店"},
    {answer: "おたなもの", question: "お店者", hint: "store employee", sound: "たな", kanji:"店"},
    // "後"
    {answer: "ほうかご", question: "放課後", hint: "after school", sound: "ご", kanji:"後"},
    {answer: "のちほど", question: "後ほど", hint: "", sound: "のち", kanji:"後"},
    {answer: "こうかい", question: "後悔", hint: "", sound: "こう", kanji:"後"},
    {answer: "うしろ", question: "後ろ", hint: "", sound: "うし", kanji:"後"},
    {answer: "あとまわし", question: "後回し", hint: "", sound: "あと", kanji:"後"},
    {answer: "たちおくれ", question: "立ち後れ", hint: "", sound: "おく", kanji:"後"},
    // "時"
    {answer: "じきしょうそう", question: "時期尚早", hint: "premature", sound: "じ", kanji:"時"},
    {answer: "ときおり", question: "時折", hint: "sometimes", sound: "とき", kanji:"時"},
    {answer: "とけい", question: "時計", hint: "clock", sound: "と", kanji:"時"},
    // "書"
    {answer: "らくがき", question: "落書き", hint: "scribble", sound: "か", kanji:"書"},
    {answer: "しょるい", question: "書類", hint: "document", sound: "しょ", kanji:"書"},
    {answer: "はがき", question: "葉書", hint: "postcard", sound: "かき", kanji:"書"},
    // "母"
    {answer: "はは", question: "母", hint: "mother", sound: "はは", kanji:"母"},
    {answer: "そぼ", question: "祖母", hint: "grandmother", sound: "ぼ", kanji:"母"},
    // "毎"
    {answer: "まいにち", question: "毎日", hint: "everyday", sound: "まい", kanji:"毎"},
    // "気"
    {answer: "きもち", question: "気持ち", hint: "feeling", sound: "き", kanji:"気"},
    {answer: "けはい", question: "気配", hint: "atmosphere", sound: "け", kanji:"気"},
    // "水"
    {answer: "しおみず", question: "塩水", hint: "salt water", sound: "みず", kanji:"水"},
    {answer: "すいえい", question: "水泳", hint: "swimming", sound: "すい", kanji:"水"},
    // "火"
    {answer: "はなび", question: "花火", hint: "firework", sound: "ひ", kanji:"火"},
    {answer: "ほてり", question: "火照り", hint: "glow", sound: "ほ", kanji:"火"},
    // "父"
    {answer: "ちち", question: "父", hint: "father", sound: "ちち", kanji:"父"},
    {answer: "そふ", question: "祖父", hint: "grandfather", sound: "ふ", kanji:"父"},
    // "生"
    {answer: "せんせい", question: "先生", hint: "teacher", sound: "せい", kanji:"生"},
    {answer: "いきる", question: "生きる", hint: "live", sound: "せい", kanji:"生"},
    {answer: "うまれる", question: "生まれる", hint: "born", sound: "う", kanji:"生"},
    {answer: "いっしょう", question: "一生", hint: "forever", sound: "しょう", kanji:"生"},
    {answer: "なまいき", question: "生意気", hint: "imputent", sound: "なま", kanji:"生"},
    {answer: "はえる", question: "生える", hint: "grow", sound: "は", kanji:"生"},
    // "男"
    {answer: "おとこ", question: "男", hint: "man", sound: "おとこ", kanji:"男"},
    {answer: "だんせい", question: "男性", hint: "male", sound: "だん", kanji:"男"},
    {answer: "ちょうなん", question: "長男", hint: "eldest son", sound: "なん", kanji:"男"},
    // "白"
    {answer: "おもしろい", question: "面白い", hint: "amusing", sound: "しろ", kanji:"白"},
    {answer: "こくはく", question: "告白", hint: "confession", sound: "はく", kanji:"白"},
    {answer: "しらゆきひめ", question: "白雪姫", hint: "snow white", sound: "しら", kanji:"白"},
    {answer: "びゃくや", question: "白夜", hint: "midnight sun", sound: "びゃく", kanji:"白"},
    {answer: "はっきん", question: "白金", hint: "platinum", sound: "はっ", kanji:"白"},
    // "百"
    {answer: "ひゃく", question: "百", hint: "hundred", sound: "ひゃく", kanji:"百"},
    {answer: "ひゃっか", question: "百科", hint: "encyclopedia", sound: "ひゃっ", kanji:"百"},
    {answer: "やおや", question: "八百屋", hint: "green grocer", sound: "お", kanji:"百"},
    // "目"
    {answer: "めざす", question: "目指す", hint: "aim", sound: "め", kanji:"目"},
    {answer: "もくてき", question: "目的", hint: "goal", sound: "もく", kanji:"目"},
    {answer: "めんぼく", question: "面目", hint: "face", sound: "ぼく", kanji:"目"},
    // "社"
    {answer: "しゃかい", question: "社会", hint: "society", sound: "しゃ", kanji:"社"},
    // "空"
    {answer: "あおそら", question: "青空", hint: "blue sky", sound: "そら", kanji:"空"},
    {answer: "くうはく", question: "空白", hint: "blank", sound: "くう", kanji:"空"},
    {answer: "おなかすく", question: "お腹空く", hint: "hungry", sound: "す", kanji:"空"},
    {answer: "からまわり", question: "空回り", hint: "going circle", sound: "から", kanji:"空"},
    {answer: "あきべや", question: "空き部屋", hint: "empty room", sound: "あ", kanji:"空"},
    // "立"
    {answer: "たつ", question: "立つ", hint: "stand up", sound: "た", kanji:"立"},
    {answer: "せいりつ", question: "成立", hint: "formed", sound: "りつ", kanji:"立"},
    {answer: "たちば", question: "立場", hint: "position", sound: "たち", kanji:"立"},
    {answer: "こんだて", question: "献立", hint: "menu", sound: "たて", kanji:"立"},
    // "耳"
    {answer: "みみ", question: "耳", hint: "ear", sound: "みみ", kanji:"耳"},
    {answer: "じび", question: "耳鼻", hint: "ear and nose", sound: "じ", kanji:"耳"},
    // "聞"
    {answer: "きく", question: "聞く", hint: "hear", sound: "き", kanji:"聞"},
    {answer: "しんぶん", question: "新聞", hint: "newspaper", sound: "ぶん", kanji:"聞"},
    // "花"
    {answer: "はな", question: "花", hint: "flower", sound: "はな", kanji:"花"},
    {answer: "かふんしょう", question: "花粉症", hint: "hay fever", sound: "か", kanji:"花"},
    // "行"
    {answer: "いく", question: "行く", hint: "go", sound: "い", kanji:"行"},
    {answer: "りょこう", question: "旅行", hint: "travel", sound: "こう", kanji:"行"},
    {answer: "おこなう", question: "行う", hint: "perform", sound: "おこな", kanji:"行"},
    {answer: "しゅぎょう", question: "修行", hint: "training", sound: "ぎょう", kanji:"行"},
    // "西"
    {answer: "にし", question: "西", hint: "west", sound: "にし", kanji:"西"},
    {answer: "かんさい", question: "関西", hint: "kansai", sound: "さい", kanji:"西"},
    {answer: "せいれき", question: "西暦", hint: "calendar", sound: "せい", kanji:"西"},
    // "見"
    {answer: "みる", question: "見る", hint: "look", sound: "み", kanji:"見"},
    {answer: "はっけん", question: "発見", hint: "discovery", sound: "けん", kanji:"見"},
    // "言"
    {answer: "いう", question: "言う", hint: "say", sound: "い", kanji:"言"},
    {answer: "ことば", question: "言葉", hint: "word", sound: "こと", kanji:"言"},
    {answer: "げんご", question: "言語", hint: "language", sound: "げん", kanji:"言"},
    {answer: "でんごん", question: "伝言", hint: "message", sound: "ごん", kanji:"言"},
    // "話"
    {answer: "はなし", question: "話し", hint: "speak", sound: "はな", kanji:"話"},
    {answer: "でんわ", question: "電話", hint: "phone call", sound: "わ", kanji:"話"},
    // "語"
    {answer: "えいご", question: "英語", hint: "language", sound: "ご", kanji:"語"},
    {answer: "かたりあう", question: "語り合う", hint: "discussion", sound: "かた", kanji:"語"},
    // "買"
    {answer: "かう", question: "買う", hint: "buy", sound: "か", kanji:"買"},
    {answer: "ばいしゅう", question: "買収", hint: "bribe", sound: "ばい", kanji:"買"},
    // "足"
    {answer: "あし", question: "足", hint: "foot", sound: "あし", kanji:"足"},
    {answer: "たりる", question: "足りる", hint: "sufficient", sound: "た", kanji:"足"},
    {answer: "えんそく", question: "遠足", hint: "trip", sound: "そく", kanji:"足"},
    // "車"
    {answer: "でんしゃ", question: "電車", hint: "train", sound: "しゃ", kanji:"車"},
    {answer: "くるま", question: "車", hint: "car", sound: "くるま", kanji:"車"},
    // "週"
    {answer: "しゅうかん", question: "週間", hint: "week", sound: "しゅう", kanji:"週"},
    // "道"
    {answer: "みち", question: "道", hint: "road", sound: "みち", kanji:"道"},
    {answer: "ほっかいどう", question: "北海道", hint: "city name", sound: "どう", kanji:"道"},
    // "金"
    {answer: "きん", question: "金", hint: "gold", sound: "きん", kanji:"金"},
    {answer: "おかね", question: "お金", hint: "money", sound: "かね", kanji:"金"},
    {answer: "おうごん", question: "黄金", hint: "golden", sound: "ごん", kanji:"金"},
    {answer: "かなもの", question: "金物", hint: "metal", sound: "かな", kanji:"金"},
    // "長"
    {answer: "しゃちょう", question: "社長", hint: "company president", sound: "ちょう", kanji:"長"},
    {answer: "ながい", question: "長い", hint: "long", sound: "なが", kanji:"長"},
    // "間"
    {answer: "なかま", question: "仲間", hint: "ally", sound: "ま", kanji:"間"},
    {answer: "じかん", question: "時間", hint: "time", sound: "かん", kanji:"間"},
    {answer: "にんげん", question: "人間", hint: "human", sound: "げん", kanji:"間"},
    {answer: "とうぶんのあいだ", question: "当分の間", hint: "for a while", sound: "あいだ", kanji:"間"},
    // "雨"
    {answer: "あめ", question: "雨", hint: "rain", sound: "あめ", kanji:"雨"},
    {answer: "あまやどり", question: "雨宿り", hint: "shelter", sound: "あま", kanji:"雨"},
    {answer: "らいう", question: "雷雨", hint: "thunder rain", sound: "う", kanji:"雨"},
    {answer: "こさめ", question: "小雨", hint: "light rain", sound: "さめ", kanji:"雨"},
    // "電"
    {answer: "でんき", question: "電気", hint: "electric", sound: "でん", kanji:"電"},
    // "食"
    {answer: "たべる", question: "食べる", hint: "eat", sound: "た", kanji:"食"},
    {answer: "くう", question: "食", hint: "eat", sound: "く", kanji:"食"},
    {answer: "しょくじ", question: "食事", hint: "food", sound: "しょく", kanji:"食"},
    {answer: "こじき", question: "乞食", hint: "beg", sound: "じき", kanji:"食"},
    // "飲"
    {answer: "のむ", question: "飲む", hint: "drink", sound: "の", kanji:"飲"},
    {answer: "いんしょくてん", question: "飲食店", hint: "restaurant", sound: "いん", kanji:"飲"},
    // "駅"
    {answer: "えき", question: "駅", hint: "station", sound: "えき", kanji:"駅"},
    // "高"
    {answer: "さいこう", question: "最高", hint: "best", sound: "こう", kanji:"高"},
    {answer: "たかい", question: "高い", hint: "high", sound: "たか", kanji:"高"},
    // "魚"
    {answer: "さかな", question: "魚", hint: "fish", sound: "さかな", kanji:"魚"},
    {answer: "にんぎょ", question: "人魚", hint: "mermaid", sound: "ぎょ", kanji:"魚"},
    {answer: "うおざ", question: "魚座", hint: "pisces", sound: "うお", kanji:"魚"},
    ////////////////////////////////////// "不"
    // "世"
    // "主"
    // "乘"
    // "事"
    // "京"
    // "仕"
    // "代"
    // "以"
    // "低"
    // "住"
    // "体"
    // "作"
    // "使"
    // "元"
    // "兄"
    // "光"
    // "写"
    // "冬"
    // "切"
    // "勉"
    // "動"
    // "区"
    // "医"
    // "去"
    // "合"
    // "合"
    // "同"
    // "味"
    // "品"
    // "員"
    // "問"
    // "回"
    // "図"
    // "地"
    // "堂"
    // "場"
    // "声"
    // "売"
    // "夏"
    // "夕"
    // "夜"
    // "太"
    // "好"
    // "妹"
    // "姉"
    // "始"
    // "字"
    // "室"
    // "家"
    // "寒"
    // "屋"
    // "工"
    // "市"
    // "帰"
    // "広"
    // "度"
    // "建"
    // "引"
    // "弟"
    // "弱"
    // "強"
    // "待"
    // "心"
    // "思"
    // "悪"
    // "意"
    // "所"
    // "持"
    // "教"
    // "文"
    // "料"
    // "方"
    // "旅"
    // "族"
    // "早"
    // "明"
    // "映"
    // "春"
    // "昼"
    // "暑"
    // "有"
    // "服"
    // "朝"
    // "村"
    // "林"
    // "森"
    // "業"
    // "楽"
    // "歌"
    // "止"
    // "正"
    // "步"
    // "死"
    // "民"
    // "池"
    // "注"
    // "洋"
    // "洗"
    // "海"
    // "漢"
    // "牛"
    // "物"
    // "特"
    // "犬"
    // "理"
    // "產"
    // "用"
    // "田"
    // "町"
    // "画"
    // "界"
    // "病"
    // "発"
    // "県"
    // "真"
    // "着"
    // "知"
    // "短"
    // "研"
    // "私"
    // "秋"
    // "究"
    // "答"
    // "紙"
    // "終"
    // "考"
    // "者"
    // "自"
    // "色"
    // "英"
    // "茶"
    // "菜"
    // "薬"
    // "親"
    // "計"
    // "試"
    // "説"
    // "貸"
    // "質"
    // "赤"
    // "転"
    // "軽"
    // "近"
    // "送"
    // "通"
    // "進"
    // "運"
    // "遠"
    // "都"
    // "重"
    // "野"
    // "銀"
    // "門"
    // "開"
    // "院"
    // "集"
    // "青"
    // "音"
    // "頭"
    // "題"
    // "顔"
    // "風"
    // "飯"
    // "館"
    // "首"
    // "験"
    // "鳥"
    // "黒"
    // "与"
    // "両"
    // "並"
    // "丸"
    // "久"
    // "乱"
    // "乳"
    // "乾"
    // "了"
    // "予"
    // "争"
    // "互"
    // "亡"
    // "交"
    // "介"
    // "仏"
    // "令"
    // "仮"
    // "仲"
    // "件"
    // "任"
    // "伝"
    // "伸"
    // "伺"
    // "似"
    // "位"
    // "余"
    // "例"
    // "供"
    // "依"
    // "価"
    // "修"
    // "個"
    // "倍"
    // "倒"
    // "候"
    // "值"
    // "偉"
    // "停"
    // "健"
    // "側"
    // "偶"
    // "備"
    // "傾"
    // "像"
    // "億"
    // "優"
    // "兆"
    // "况"
    // "党"
    // "全"
    // "公"
    // "共"
    // "兵"
    // "具"
    // "内"
    // "冊"
    // "再"
    // "冷"
    // "凍"
    // "処"
    // "刊"
    // "列"
    // "初"
    // "判"
    // "利"
    // "到"
    // "制"
    // "刷"
    // "券"
    // "刺"
    // "刻"
    // "則"
    // "副"
    // "割"
    // "劇"
    // "助"
    // "努"
    // "労"
    // "効"
    // "勇"
    // "務"
    // "勝"
    // "募"
    // "勢"
    // "勤"
    // "包"
    // "化"
    // "匹"
    // "卒"
    // "協"
    // "危"
    // "卵"
    // "厚"
    // "原"
    // "参"
    // "双"
    // "反"
    // "收"
    // "取"
    // "受"
    // "叫"
    // "召"
    // "可"
    {answer: "かわい", question: "可愛い", hint: "cute", sound: "か", kanji:"可"},
    {answer: "かのうせい", question: "可能性", hint: "possibility", sound: "か", kanji:"可"},
    // "史"
    // "号"
    // "司"
    // "各"
    // "向"
    // "君"
    // "否"
    // "含"
    // "吸"
    // "吹"
    // "告"
    // "周"
    // "呼"
    // "命"
    // "和"
    // "咲"
    // "商"
    // "善"
    // "喜"
    // "喫"
    // "学"
    // "器"
    // "因"
    // "团"
    // "困"
    // "围"
    // "固"
    // "園"
    // "压"
    // "在"
    // "坂"
    // "均"
    // "型"
    // "埋"
    // "城"
    // "域"
    // "基"
    // "報"
    // "塔"
    // "塗"
    // "塩"
    // "境"
    // "増"
    // "壁"
    // "変"
    // "夢"
    // "夫"
    // "央"
    // "失"
    // "妻"
    // "姓"
    // "委"
    // "娘"
    // "婚"
    // "婦"
    // "存"
    // "李"
    // "孫"
    // "宅"
    // "宇"
    // "守"
    // "完"
    // "官"
    // "宙"
    // "定"
    // "宝"
    // "実"
    // "客"
    // "害"
    // "容"
    // "宿"
    // "寄"
    // "富"
    // "寝"
    // "察"
    // "寺"
    // "对"
    // "封"
    // "專"
    // "将"
    // "尊"
    // "導"
    // "局"
    // "居"
    // "届"
    // "展"
    // "層"
    // "岩"
    // "岸"
    // "島"
    // "州"
    // "巨"
    // "差"
    // "卷"
    // "布"
    // "希"
    // "師"
    // "席"
    // "带"
    // "常"
    // "帽"
    // "幅"
    // "干"
    // "平"
    // "幸"
    // "幼"
    // "厅"
    // "床"
    // "底"
    // "府"
    // "座"
    // "庫"
    // "康"
    // "延"
    // "式"
    // "張"
    // "当"
    // "形"
    // "役"
    // "彼"
    // "律"
    // "徒"
    // "得"
    // "御"
    // "復"
    // "必"
    // "志"
    // "忘"
    // "忙"
    // "应"
    // "快"
    // "念"
    // "怒"
    // "怖"
    // "性"
    // "恋"
    // "恐"
    // "恥"
    // "息"
    // "惠"
    // "忷"
    // "悲"
    // "情"
    // "想"
    // "愛"
    {answer: "あい", question: "愛", hint: "love", sound: "あい", kanji:"愛"},
    {answer: "いとしい", question: "愛しい", hint: "beloved", sound: "いと", kanji:"愛"},
    {answer: "まなむすめ", question: "愛娘", hint: "favorite daughter", sound: "まな", kanji:"愛"},
    // "感"
    // "慣"
    // "憎"
    // "成"
    // "戰"
    // "戶"
    // "戾"
    // "才"
    // "打"
    // "扒"
    // "批"
    // "承"
    // "技"
    // "投"
    // "折"
    // "扳"
    // "抱"
    // "押"
    // "担"
    // "招"
    // "挥"
    // "抗"
    // "拾"
    // "指"
    // "挟"
    // "捕"
    // "搜"
    // "拾"
    // "掃"
    // "採"
    // "探"
    // "接"
    // "換"
    // "損"
    // "操"
    // "支"
    // "改"
    // "放"
    // "政"
    // "故"
    // "救"
    // "敗"
    // "散"
    // "敬"
    // "数"
    // "整"
    // "断"
    // "旧"
    // "昇"
    // "易"
    // "昔"
    // "星"
    // "昨"
    // "晚"
    // "普"
    // "景"
    // "晴"
    // "暖"
    // "暮"
    // "暴"
    // "曇"
    // "曲"
    // "更"
    // "替"
    // "最"
    // "望"
    // "期"
    // "未"
    // "末"
    // "札"
    // "机"
    // "材"
    // "束"
    // "条"
    // "杯"
    // "板"
    // "枚"
    // "果"
    // "枝"
    // "枯"
    // "柔"
    // "柱"
    // "查"
    // "栄"
    // "根"
    // "格"
    // "案"
    // "械"
    // "棒"
    // "植"
    // "檢"
    // "様"
    // "標"
    // "権"
    // "横"
    // "橋"
    // "機"
    // "欠"
    // "迩"
    // "欧"
    // "欲"
    // "武"
    // "歯"
    // "歳"
    // "歴"
    // "残"
    // "段"
    // "殺"
    // "殿"
    // "毒"
    // "比"
    // "毛"
    // "氷"
    // "永"
    // "求"
    // "汗"
    // "汚"
    // "決"
    // "沈"
    // "河"
    // "沸"
    // "油"
    // "治"
    // "況"
    // "泉"
    // "泊"
    // "法"
    // "波"
    // "泣"
    // "泥"
    // "泳"
    // "活"
    // "流"
    // "浅"
    // "浮"
    // "浴"
    // "消"
    // "涙"
    // "液"
    // "涼"
    // "深"
    // "混"
    // "清"
    // "済"
    // "減"
    // "渡"
    // "温"
    // "測"
    // "港"
    // "湖"
    // "湯"
    // "湾"
    // "溶"
    // "滴"
    // "漁"
    // "演"
    // "濃"
    // "濯"
    // "灯"
    // "灰"
    // "炭"
    // "点"
    // "無"
    // "然"
    // "燒"
    // "煙"
    // "照"
    // "熱"
    // "燃"
    // "燥"
    // "爆"
    // "片"
    // "版"
    // "犯"
    // "状"
    // "独"
    // "狭"
    // "猫"
    // "率"
    // "玉"
    // "王"
    // "珍"
    // "現"
    // "球"
    // "環"
    // "甘"
    // "由"
    // "申"
    // "畑"
    // "留"
    // "畜"
    // "略"
    // "番"
    // "異"
    // "置"
    // "疑"
    // "疲"
    // "痛"
    // "療"
    // "登"
    // "的"
    // "示"
    // "礼"
    // "祈"
    // "祖"
    // "祝"
    // "神"
    // "祭"
    // "禁"
    // "福"
    // "科"
    // "秒"
    // "移"
    // "程"
    // "税"
    // "種"
    // "積"
    // "突"
    // "窓"
    // "章"
    // "童"
    // "競"
    // "竹"
    // "笑"
    // "符"
    // "第"
    // "筆"
    // "等"
    // "筒"
    // "算"
    // "管"
    // "箱"
    // "節"
    // "築"
    // "簡"
    // "米"
    // "粉"
    // "粒"
    // "精"
    // "糸"
    // "約"
    // "紅"
    // "純"
    // "級"
    // "細"
    // "紹"
    // "組"
    // "經"
    // "結"
    // "絡"
    // "美"
    // "群"
    // "羽"
    // "翌"
    // "老"
    // "耕"
    // "職"
    // "肌"
    // "肩"
    // "肯"
    // "育"
    // "胃"
    // "背"
    // "胸"
    // "能"
    // "脂"
    // "脳"
    // "腕"
    // "腰"
    // "腹"
    // "膚"
    // "臓"
    // "臣"
    // "舞"
    // "舟"
    // "航"
    // "般"
    // "船"
    // "良"
    // "芸"
    // "若"
    // "苦"
    // "草"
    // "荒"
    // "荷"
    // "菓"
    // "落"
    // "葉"
    // "著"
    // "蒸"
    // "蔵"
    // "薄"
    // "虫"
    // "血"
    // "術"
    // "衣"
    // "表"
    // "袋"
    // "被"
    // "装"
    // "設"
    // "許"
    // "評"
    // "詞"
    // "詰"
    // "誌"
    // "認"
    // "誤"
    // "課"
    // "調"
    // "談"
    // "論"
    // "諸"
    // "講"
    // "識"
    // "警"
    // "議"
    // "谷"
    // "豊"
    // "象"
    // "貝"
    // "負"
    // "財"
    // "貧"
    // "貨"
    // "販"
    // "責"
    // "貯"
    // "費"
    // "貿"
    // "賃"
    // "資"
    // "賛"
    // "賞"
    // "賢"
    // "贈"
    // "超"
    // "越"
    // "路"
    // "踊"
    // "身"
    // "軍"
    // "軒"
    // "軟"
    // "較"
    // "輪"
    // "輸"
    // "辛"
    // "辞"
    // "農"
    // "遲"
    // "遊"
    // "過"
    // "達"
    // "違"
    // "適"
    // "選"
    // "郊"
    // "部"
    // "郵"
    // "配"
    // "酒"
    // "量"
    // "針"
    // "鈍"
    // "鉄"
    // "鈜"
    // "銅"
    // "銳"
    // "鍒"
    // "閉"
    // "関"
    // "防"
    // "降"
    // "限"
    // "除"
    // "陸"
    // "陇"
    // "陽"
    // "隅"
    // "階"
    // "際"
    // "雇"
    // "雜"
    // "難"
    // "雪"
    // "雲"
    // "零"
    // "震"
    // "静"
    // "非"
    // "面"
    // "革"
    // "靴"
    // "頂"
    // "順"
    // "預"
    // "領"
    // "頛"
    // "丈"
    // "丘"
    // "丙"
    // "丹"
    // "乏"
    // "乙"
    // "井"
    // "亞"
    // "享"
    // "亭"
    // "仁"
    // "仙"
    // "仰"
    // "企"
    // "伏"
    // "伐"
    // "伯"
    // "伴"
    // "佐"
    // "佳"
    // "併"
    // "侍"
    // "悔"
    // "侵"
    // "促"
    // "俊"
    // "俗"
    // "俳"
    // "俵"
    // "俸"
    // "倉"
    // "做"
    // "倫"
    // "偏"
    // "偵"
    // "偽"
    // "傍"
    // "傑"
    // "傘"
    // "催"
    // "債"
    // "傷"
    // "僕"
    // "僚"
    // "僧"
    // "儀"
    // "儒"
    // "償"
    // "刃"
    // "刈"
    // "刑"
    // "削"
    // "剖"
    // "剛"
    // "剣"
    // "剤"
    // "剰"
    // "創"
    // "功"
    // "劣"
    // "励"
    // "劾"
    // "勅"
    // "勘"
    // "勧"
    // "勲"
    // "匠"
    // "匿"
    // "升"
    // "卑"
    // "卓"
    // "博"
    // "即"
    // "却"
    // "卸"
    // "厄"
    // "厘"
    // "厳"
    // "又"
    // "及"
    // "叔"
    // "叙"
    // "句"
    // "吉"
    // "后"
    // "吏"
    // "吐"
    // "吟"
    // "呈"
    // "呉"
    // "哀"
    // "哲"
    // "唆"
    // "唇"
    // "唐"
    // "唯"
    // "唱"
    // "啓"
    // "喚"
    // "培"
    // "堀"
    // "堅"
    // "堕"
    // "堤"
    // "堪"
    // "塀"
    // "曌"
    // "塊"
    // "塑"
    // "塚"
    // "塾"
    // "墓"
    // "墜"
    // "墨"
    // "墳"
    // "墾"
    // "壇"
    // "壞"
    // "壤"
    // "士"
    // "壮"
    // "志"
    // "奇"
    // "奉"
    // "奏"
    // "契"
    // "奔"
    // "獎"
    // "奪"
    // "奮"
    // "如"
    // "妃"
    // "妄"
    // "妊"
    // "妙"
    // "妥"
    // "妨"
    // "姫"
    // "姻"
    // "姿"
    // "威"
    // "娠"
    // "娛"
    // "婿"
    // "媒"
    // "嫁"
    // "嫌"
    // "嫡"
    // "孃"
    // "手"
    // "便"
    // "新"
    // "借"
    // "日"
    // "軍"
    // "一"
    // "急"
    // "習"
    // "付"
    // "暗"
    // "走"
    // "加"
    // "坊"
    // "係"
    // "单"
    // "保"
    // "占"
    // "絵"
    // "裏"
    // "額"
    // "充"
    // "一"
    // "願"
    // "克"
    // "皿"
    // "絶"
    // "補"
    // "込"
    // "類"
    // "免"
    // "紛"
    // "製"
    // "迎"
    // "飛"
    // "典"
    // "綿"
    // "複"
    // "返"
    // "香"
    // "兼"
    // "角"
    // "逃"
    // "績"
    // "触"
    // "途"
    // "黄"
    // "、"
    // "喪"
    // "孤"
    // "月"
    // "木"
    // "本"
    // "来"
    // "東"
    // "校"
    // "1"
    // "別"
    // "力"
    // "曜"
    // "起"
    // "信"
    // "印"
    // "奥"
    // "庭"
    // "授"
    // "掘"
    // "極"
    // "構"
    // "湿"
    // "満"
    // "硬"
    // "準"
    // "皆"
    // "皮"
    // "盗"
    // "直"
    // "相"
    // "省"
    // "看"
    // "眠"
    // "石"
    // "砂"
    // "破"
    // "総"
    // "緑"
    // "緖"
    // "線"
    // "編"
    // "練"
    // "確"
    // "磨"
    // "給"
    // "罪"
    // "置"
    // "署"
    // "要"
    // "規"
    // "覚"
    // "観"
    // "解"
    // "訓"
    // "記"
    // "訪"
    // "述"
    // "追"
    // "退"
    // "逆"
    // "速"
    // "造"
    // "連"
    // "馬"
    // "駐"
    // "骨"
    // "冗"
    // "髮"
    // "鳴"
    // "冒"
    // "冠"
    // "麦"
    // "鼻"
    // "齢"
    // "丁"
    // "准"
    // "凝"
    // "凡"
    // "凶"
    // "凸"
    // "凹"
    // "刀"
    // "喝"
    // "嗣"
    // "嘆"
    // "嘱"
    // "噴"
    // "囚"
    // "圈"
    // "坑"
    // "坪"
    // "垂"
    // "垣"
    // "執"
    // "宗"
    // "宜"
    // "宣"
    // "宮"
    // "宰"
    // "宴"
    // "宵"
    // "寂"
    // "密"
    // "寛"
    // "寧"
    // "審"
    // "寮"
    // "寸"
    // "寿"
    // "射"
    // "尉"
    // "尋"
    // "尚"
    // "就"
    // "尺"
    // "尼"
    // "尽"
    // "尾"
    // "尿"
    // "屈"
    // "属"
    // "履"
    // "屯"
    // "歧"
    // "岬"
    // "岳"
    // "峠"
    // "峡"
    // "峰"
    // "崇"
    // "崎"
    // "崩"
    // "巡"
    // "巣"
    // "巧"
    // "已"
    // "帆"
    // "帝"
    // "帳"
    // "幕"
    // "幣"
    // "幹"
    // "幻"
    // "幽"
    // "幾"
    // "序"
    // "庶"
    // "庸"
    // "廃"
    // "廉"
    // "廊"
    // "廷"
    // "弁"
    // "弊"
    // "弐"
    // "弓"
    // "弔"
    // "弦"
    // "弧"
    // "弾"
    // "彩"
    // "彫"
    // "彰"
    // "影"
    // "往"
    // "征"
    // "径"
    // "徐"
    // "從"
    // "循"
    // "微"
    // "徳"
    // "徵"
    // "徹"
    // "忌"
    // "忍"
    // "忠"
    // "怠"
    // "怪"
    // "恒"
    // "恨"
    // "恩"
    // "恭"
    // "悔"
    // "悟"
    // "悠"
    // "患"
    // "悦"
    // "悼"
    // "惑"
    // "惜"
    // "惨"
    // "惰"
    // "愁"
    // "愉"
    // "愚"
    // "慈"
    // "態"
    // "慌"
    // "慎"
    // "慕"
    // "慢"
    // "慨"
    // "慮"
    // "慰"
    // "慶"
    // "憂"
    // "憤"
    // "憩"
    // "憲"
    // "憶"
    // "憾"
    // "懇"
    // "懐"
    // "懲"
    // "懸"
    // "我"
    // "戒"
    // "戱"
    // "房"
    // "扇"
    // "扉"
    // "扱"
    // "扶"
    // "抄"
    // "把"
    // "抑"
    // "抗"
    // "护"
    // "披"
    // "抵"
    // "抹"
    // "抽"
    // "拍"
    // "拐"
    // "拒"
    // "拓"
    // "拘"
    // "拙"
    // "挻"
    // "括"
    // "拷"
    // "挑"
    // "举"
    // "振"
    // "揮"
    // "据"
    // "掌"
    // "排"
    // "掛"
    // "控"
    // "推"
    // "猎"
    // "揭"
    // "描"
    // "提"
    // "揚"
    // "握"
    // "揮"
    // "援"
    // "摇"
    // "搬"
    // "搭"
    // "携"
    // "搾"
    // "掑"
    // "摘"
    // "摩"
    // "擊"
    // "撤"
    // "撮"
    // "撲"
    // "擁"
    // "擦"
    // "擬"
    // "攻"
    // "敏"
    // "敢"
    // "敵"
    // "敷"
    // "斉"
    // "斋"
    // "斗"
    // "斜"
    // "斤"
    // "斥"
    // "施"
    // "旋"
    // "旗"
    // "既"
    // "旨"
    // "旬"
    // "昆"
    // "昭"
    // "是"
    // "晶"
    // "暁"
    // "暇"
    // "暦"
    // "暫"
    // "曹"
    // "朗"
    // "朱"
    // "朴"
    // "朽"
    // "杉"
    // "松"
    // "析"
    // "枠"
    // "枢"
    // "架"
    // "柄"
    // "某"
    // "染"
    // "柳"
    // "栓"
    // "株"
    // "核"
    // "栽"
    // "桃"
    // "桑"
    // "桜"
    // "桟"
    // "梅"
    // "棄"
    // "棋"
    // "棚"
    // "棟"
    // "棺"
    // "楼"
    // "概"
    // "槽"
    // "模"
    // "樹"
    // "欄"
    // "欺"
    // "款"
    // "歓"
    // "殉"
    // "殊"
    // "殖"
    // "殴"
    // "殻"
    // "氏"
    // "汁"
    // "江"
    // "汽"
    // "沖"
    // "没"
    // "沢"
    // "沼"
    // "沿"
    // "泌"
    // "泡"
    // "泰"
    // "洞"
    // "津"
    // "洪"
    // "派"
    // "浄"
    // "浜"
    // "浦"
    // "浪"
    // "浸"
    // "涯"
    // "淑"
    // "淡"
    // "添"
    // "渴"
    // "涉"
    // "谈"
    // "溪"
    // "渦"
    // "源"
    // "溝"
    // "滅"
    // "滋"
    // "滑"
    // "滝"
    // "滞"
    // "漂"
    // "漆"
    // "漏"
    // "漠"
    // "漫"
    // "漬"
    // "漸"
    // "潔"
    // "潜"
    // "潟"
    // "潤"
    // "潮"
    // "澄"
    // "激"
    // "濁"
    // "濫"
    // "瀬"
    // "災"
    // "炉"
    // "炊"
    // "炎"
    // "為"
    // "烈"
    // "焦"
    // "煩"
    // "煮"
    // "熟"
    // "牧"
    // "牲"
    // "犧"
    // "狂"
    // "狩"
    // "猛"
    // "獵"
    // "献"
    // "猶"
    // "猿"
    // "獄"
    // "獸"
    // "獲"
    // "玄"
    // "珠"
    // "班"
    // "琴"
    // "垔"
    // "瓶"
    // "甚"
    // "甲"
    // "畔"
    // "疎"
    // "疫"
    // "疾"
    // "症"
    // "痘"
    // "痢"
    // "痴"
    // "癒"
    // "癖"
    // "皇"
    // "盆"
    // "益"
    // "盛"
    // "盟"
    // "監"
    // "盤"
    // "盲"
    // "盾"
    // "眺"
    // "眼"
    // "睡"
    // "督"
    // "瞬"
    // "矛"
    // "矢"
    // "矯"
    // "碎"
    // "砲"
    // "硝"
    // "硫"
    // "碁"
    // "碑"
    // "磁"
    // "礁"
    // "礎"
    // "祉"
    // "祥"
    // "票"
    // "禅"
    // "禍"
    // "秀"
    // "秘"
    // "租"
    // "秩"
    // "称"
    // "稚"
    // "稲"
    // "稼"
    // "稿"
    // "榖"
    // "穗"
    // "稳"
    // "穫"
    // "穴"
    // "窃"
    // "窒"
    // "窮"
    // "窯"
    // "竜"
    // "端"
    // "笛"
    // "筋"
    // "策"
    // "箇"
    // "範"
    // "篤"
    // "簿"
    // "籍"
    // "粋"
    // "粗"
    // "粘"
    // "粛"
    // "粧"
    // "糖"
    // "糧"
    // "系"
    // "糾"
    // "紀"
    // "紋"
    // "納"
    // "紛"
    // "素"
    // "紡"
    // "索"
    // "紫"
    // "累"
    // "紳"
    // "紺"
    // "絞"
    // "統"
    // "絹"
    // "継"
    // "維"
    // "綱"
    // "網"
    // "緊"
    // "締"
    // "緩"
    // "緯"
    // "縁"
    // "縄"
    // "縛"
    // "縦"
    // "縫"
    // "縮"
    // "繁"
    // "繊"
    // "織"
    // "繕"
    // "繭"
    // "繰"
    // "缶"
    // "罰"
    // "罷"
    // "羅"
    // "羊"
    // "義"
    // "翻"
    // "翼"
    // "耐"
    // "耗"
    // "聖"
    // "聴"
    // "肖"
    // "肝"
    // "肢"
    // "肥"
    // "肪"
    // "肺"
    // "胆"
    // "胎"
    // "胞"
    // "胴"
    // "脅"
    // "脈"
    // "脚"
    // "脱"
    // "腐"
    // "腸"
    // "膜"
    // "膨"
    // "臨"
    // "臭"
    // "至"
    // "致"
    // "興"
    // "舌"
    // "舍"
    // "舖"
    // "舶"
    // "艇"
    // "艦"
    // "芋"
    // "芝"
    // "芳"
    // "芽"
    // "苗"
    // "茂"
    // "茎"
    // "茌"
    // "菊"
    // "菌"
    // "華"
    // "葬"
    // "蓄"
    // "薦"
    // "薰"
    // "藩"
    // "藻"
    // "虐"
    // "虛"
    // "虜"
    // "蚊"
    // "蚕"
    // "蛇"
    // "茧"
    // "蛮"
    // "融"
    // "衆"
    // "街"
    // "衛"
    // "衝"
    // "衡"
    // "衰"
    // "衷"
    // "裁"
    // "裂"
    // "裕"
    // "裸"
    // "褐"
    // "褒"
    // "襟"
    // "襲"
    // "覆"
    // "覇"
    // "視"
    // "覧"
    // "訂"
    // "討"
    // "託"
    // "訟"
    // "訳"
    // "訴"
    // "診"
    // "証"
    // "詐"
    // "詔"
    // "詠"
    // "詩"
    // "該"
    // "詳"
    // "誇"
    // "誉"
    // "誓"
    // "誕"
    // "誘"
    // "誠"
    // "請"
    // "諭"
    // "諮"
    // "諾"
    // "謀"
    // "謁"
    // "謄"
    // "謙"
    // "謝"
    // "謡"
    // "謹"
    // "譜"
    // "譲"
    // "護"
    // "豆"
    // "豚"
    // "豪"
    // "貞"
    // "貢"
    // "貫"
    // "貴"
    // "賀"
    // "賄"
    // "賊"
    // "賓"
    // "賜"
    // "賠"
    // "賦"
    // "購"
    // "赦"
    // "赴"
    // "趣"
    // "距"
    // "跡"
    // "跳"
    // "践"
    // "踏"
    // "躍"
    // "軌"
    // "軸"
    // "載"
    // "輝"
    // "輩"
    // "轄"
    // "辱"
    // "迅"
    // "迫"
    // "迭"
    // "透"
    // "逐"
    // "遤"
    // "逝"
    // "逮"
    // "逸"
    // "遂"
    // "遇"
    // "遍"
    // "遣"
    // "遭"
    // "遮"
    // "遵"
    // "遷"
    // "遺"
    // "避"
    // "還"
    // "邦"
    // "邪"
    // "邸"
    // "郎"
    // "郡"
    // "郭"
    // "鄊"
    // "酌"
    // "醉"
    // "酢"
    // "酪"
    // "酬"
    // "酵"
    // "酷"
    // "酸"
    // "醜"
    // "釀"
    // "积"
    // "里"
    // "釣"
    // "鈴"
    // "鉛"
    // "鉢"
    // "銃"
    // "銘"
    // "銬"
    // "鋳"
    // "鋼"
    // "錠"
    // "鍊"
    // "錯"
    // "鍛"
    // "鎖"
    // "鎮"
    // "鏡"
    // "鐘"
    // "鑑"
    // "閑"
    // "閣"
    // "閥"
    // "閲"
    // "闘"
    // "阻"
    // "附"
    // "陛"
    // "陣"
    // "陥"
    // "陪"
    // "陰"
    // "陳"
    // "陵"
    // "陶"
    // "隆"
    // "隊"
    // "随"
    // "隔"
    // "障"
    // "隠"
    // "隣"
    // "隻"
    // "雄"
    // "雅"
    // "雌"
    // "離"
    // "雰"
    // "雷"
    // "需"
    // "霊"
    // "霜"
    // "霧"
    // "露"
    // "韻"
    // "響"
    // "項"
    // "頑"
    // "頒"
    // "頻"
    // "顕"
    // "顧"
    // "飢"
    // "飼"
    // "飽"
    // "飾"
    // "養"
    // "餓"
    // "駄"
    // "駆"
    // "騎"
    // "騒"
    // "騰"
    // "騖"
    // "髄"
    // "鬼"
    // "魂"
    // "魅"
    // "魔"
    // "鮮"
    // "鯨"
    // "鶏"
    // "麗"
    // "麻"
    // "黙"
    // "鼓"
    // "翁"
    // "虞"
    // "嚇"
    // "且"
    // "侯"
    // "勺"
    // "爵"
    // "薪"
    // "帥"
    // "錘"
    // "畝"
    // "銑"
    // "但"
    // "脹"
    // "朕"
    // "奴"
    // "婆"
    // "匁"
    // "隷"
]
